techswizz.com 2019-05-19

# Privacy Policy ~ Techswizz

This Privacy Policy entails how Techswizz collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from every visitors and user of the blog. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Techswizz. It is assumed that Users still interacting with the platform has Read and Accepted the privacy policy stated below.

## Personal identification information

The personal identification information may be collected from Users using different approaches such as, but not limited to, when they place an order, subscribe to our post updates, fill out a form, etc. As appropriate, Users may be requested in such cases for their, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Personal identification information of Users is only collected when they voluntarily submit such information to us. This given information will not be disclosed to a third party without prior notice for consent to the User that owns them.

### Non-personal Identification Information (Log Files)

Non-personal identification information (log files) of Users may be collected whenever they interact with our Site. Such information may include; the internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and a number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. The non-personal identification information is not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Web Browser Cookies**  
Techswizz may use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, records user-specific information on which pages a user access or visits, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. Users may choose to set their web browsers to reject cookies or to alert them when cookies are being sent. However, if they do so, some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**Third Party Websites**  
Users may find adverts or other content on our Site that links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the contents or links that appear on these sites and therefore not responsible and liable for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. Also, these sites or services, including their contents and links, may constantly be changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies, terms of use, about, contact information and other customer service policies for you to refer to.

**Advertising**  
Ads appearing on Techswizz, purposed for monetization, may be delivered to Users by advertising partners or third parties that may collect and use cookies. These cookies allow the servers of this third-party ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**  
Ads on Techswizz may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables the company to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “no personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as contact info, health, and marital status, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting Google’s “ad and content network privacy policy” contained [here](https://www.techswizz.com/privacy-policy/?xurl=ZvQAPLG5ngxZ1Ixp6z%2F1nqeeiGTrGc8jIIcss8CyFhJqKEio7gzifsTpxL43Mphcf4ooKvjLQZdNYqLzMDjkM%2ByMzQ2HK97OIkw%2FYXUoS%2Fzb4hAMxM9ZzJnWcNgvsPURb8LoswwAZOhhOe7kAlpVbxZtn4wc3Fz%2BKlDojfNalWai8sISQsk%2FGG0Vw4P%2BAd4ZK1LEw5s%2BmqK6cUc4qkrABQ%3D%3D).

This privacy policy is subject to change or modification at any time. When such is done, notifications will be put in place. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us on Techswizzofficial.com
